const questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'Who was the first President of India?',
        answer: 'Dr. Rajendra Prasad',
        options: [
            'Jawaharlal Nehru',
            'Dr. Rajendra Prasad',
            'Sardar Patel',
            'Indira Gandhi',
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:
            "The famous 'Jallianwala Bagh massacre' took place in which city?",
        answer: 'Amritsar',
        options: ['Delhi', 'Mumbai', 'Amritsar', 'Kolkata'],
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who was known as the 'Iron Man of India'?",
        answer: 'Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel',
        options: [
            'Jawaharlal Nehru',
            'Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel',
            'Subhas Chandra Bose',
            'Lal Bahadur Shastri',
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:
            'The Indian National Army (INA) was formed by which leader during World War II?',
        answer: 'Subhas Chandra Bose',
        options: [
            'Mahatma Gandhi',
            'Subhas Chandra Bose',
            'Bhagat Singh',
            'Jawaharlal Nehru',
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:
            'The ancient city of Mohenjo-daro is part of which ancient civilization?',
        answer: 'Indus Valley Civilization',
        options: [
            'Vedic Civilization',
            'Maurya Empire',
            'Gupta Empire',
            'Indus Valley Civilization',
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:
            'Who was the first Emperor of the Maurya Dynasty in ancient India?',
        answer: 'Chandragupta Maurya',
        options: [
            'Ashoka the Great',
            'Chandragupta Maurya',
            'Bindusara',
            'Chanakya',
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:
            'The Indus Valley Civilization was primarily located in which modern-day country?',
        answer: 'Pakistan',
        options: ['India', 'Pakistan', 'Bangladesh', 'Nepal'],
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: 'Who was the first woman Prime Minister of India?',
        answer: 'Indira Gandhi',
        options: [
            'Sonia Gandhi',
            'Indira Gandhi',
            'Pratibha Patil',
            'Mamata Banerjee',
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: 'The Battle of Plassey took place in which year?',
        answer: '1757',
        options: ['1764', '1757', '1857', '1675'],
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: 'Who was the founder of the Gupta Empire?',
        answer: 'Sri Gupta',
        options: ['Chandragupta Maurya', 'Sri Gupta', 'Samudragupta', 'Ashoka'],
    },
    // {
    //     numb: 11,
    //     question: 'The Quit India Movement was launched in which year?',
    //     answer: '1942',
    //     options: ['1930', '1942', '1922', '1956'],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 12,
    //     question:
    //         "The famous 'Dandi March' led by Mahatma Gandhi was a protest against?",
    //     answer: 'Salt Tax',
    //     options: ['Indigo Tax', 'Salt Tax', 'Land Tax', 'Income Tax'],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 13,
    //     question: 'Who was the first Mughal emperor of India?',
    //     answer: 'Babur',
    //     options: ['Akbar', 'Babur', 'Humayun', 'Jahangir'],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 14,
    //     question: 'The Red Fort in Delhi was built by which Mughal Emperor?',
    //     answer: 'Shah Jahan',
    //     options: ['Akbar', 'Aurangzeb', 'Shah Jahan', 'Jahangir'],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 15,
    //     question: 'The Indian National Congress was founded in which year?',
    //     answer: '1885',
    //     options: ['1857', '1901', '1885', '1920'],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 16,
    //     question: 'Who was the first Sikh Guru?',
    //     answer: 'Guru Nanak',
    //     options: [
    //         'Guru Nanak',
    //         'Guru Gobind Singh',
    //         'Guru Angad',
    //         'Guru Tegh Bahadur',
    //     ],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 17,
    //     question:
    //         'The ancient university of Nalanda was located in which present-day Indian state?',
    //     answer: 'Bihar',
    //     options: ['Uttar Pradesh', 'Bihar', 'Madhya Pradesh', 'Rajasthan'],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 18,
    //     question:
    //         'Who was the famous queen of the Maratha-ruled state of Jhansi?',
    //     answer: 'Rani Lakshmibai',
    //     options: [
    //         'Rani Padmini',
    //         'Rani Lakshmibai',
    //         'Rani Durgavati',
    //         'Rani Ahilyabai Holkar',
    //     ],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 19,
    //     question:
    //         'The first war of Indian independence, also known as the Sepoy Mutiny, occurred in which year?',
    //     answer: '1857',
    //     options: ['1757', '1857', '1947', '1601'],
    // },
    // {
    //     numb: 20,
    //     question: "Who was the architect of the 'Constitution of India'?",
    //     answer: 'B.R. Ambedkar',
    //     options: [
    //         'Jawaharlal Nehru',
    //         'Sardar Patel',
    //         'B.R. Ambedkar',
    //         'Rajendra Prasad',
    //     ],
    // },
];
